Modern people have many wishes
Let me tell you the simplest one
Hope for daily life
Talking and laughing during the day
Get a good night's sleep
What is the result?
The body does not sleep at night
Daytime mental breakdown
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I'm your old friend, Dr. Hu.
Sleep is the most effective way
for the body
to recover and the brain to clear waste.
Especially when you fall into deep sleep
while sleeping soundly
The brain starts cleaning mode
Excrete waste
Today I want to share with you three
Ways to help you fall asleep
Acupuncture points for deep sleep
Foods for Sleep
as well as the top-level sleep technique
I've practiced for over 20 years
which has been scientifically proven effective
Which acupoints should I press for insomnia?
Hand 1 acupoint will bring your mind back to its place
One person has two selves
One awake in the dark
One sleeping in the light
Another one is on the bed, scrolling through the phone
Slide until 2am
Using your phone until 2 a.m.
If you are the kind of person
whose body is exhausted
but whose head is still beeping
Try it tonight
This super practical sleeping acupoint
This acupoint is called
Shénmén(transliteration), also known as the ānshén(transliteration) acupoint
It is an important channel between the heart and Shén(transliteration).
It calms the mind and soothes the emotions
Helps with sleep
Hey Beautiful wife
Do you know where the Shénmén(transliteration) acupoint is?
I know
Here
Wow awesome
You all know
Of course
Really great
Let me demonstrate
Acupoint pressing method
Your wrist lines
On this wrist line
Little finger and ring finger
On this line between
Connect to this horizontal stripe
This acupoint is called Shénmén(transliteration) acupoint.
Press this acupoint
Is there a
A sour and numb feeling
If there is
Just press it. Great!
As good as my beautiful wife
Press before bed
Left and right Shénmén(transliteration) acupoint
One or two minutes each
Has a relaxing effect
Especially for those who are prone to dreaming
Especially effective for people who have trouble sleeping
There is an advertisement below
I'll tell you after the ad
Let me sleep soundly
The secret to a good spirit
This habit
Let me sleep well every night and stay healthy
There is no so-called three highs
Sleeping is like
Help clean the brain
The home we live in
Also need to clean and wash frequently
There is a cleaning product
Introducing it to you
Recently, the editor gave me this bottle
Wàn néng qù zì bà(transliteration)
I just wanted to give it a try.
Results
It’s really great!
Mothers understand
Fried fish
After deep-frying the pork ribs
Oil sprays everywhere
Gas stoves and range hoods
There's a thick layer of grease.
Like this stainless steel pot
cooked to a dark color
Now
I use this bottle
Wàn néng qù zì bà(transliteration)
Spray it
Wait five minutes
You use a rag or sponge
Brush
Remove grease and char
Clean
The whole kitchen is very clean!
One time, the editor drank coffee
Spilled on shirt
I use this bottle of qù zì bà (transliteration)
Spray it
Rub it
Coffee stains cleaned
Mothers with children
Children's clothes will be stained
Various colored pencil colors
Dipped in soy sauce
You use this bottle of qù zì bà (transliteration)
Spray it
Remove various pigments
It uses a U.S. orange oil enzyme formula.
Not pungent
No fluorescent agent
Phosphorus-free
It makes people feel at ease when using it
From kitchen
bathroom to clothes
This bottle
Sān xīn lì jié wàn néng qù zì bà(transliteration)
You can handle all the cleaning tasks at home
20 Foods That Help You Sleep
Increase melatonin secretion
Do you have this symptom?
Sleeping late at night
Light sleep and poor sleep
Go to work during the day
A person is in the office
but not doing any work
A salary thief
How does Traditional Chinese Medicine view sleep?
Insomnia is mostly related to
Xīn shén bù níng yīn xuè bù zú (transliteration)
Want to sleep well
Just calm your mind
Sufficient Qi and blood
Xīnshén bù níng(transliteration)person
What to eat
will sleep better
Common sleep-inducing ingredients in Traditional Chinese Medicine
Lily Bulbs forQīng xīn ān shén(transliteration)
lotus seedsBǔ pí yǎng xīn(transliteration)
Suanzaorensis seedsYǎng gān xiě ān shén dìng zhì(transliteration)
Paired with millet, black sesame, longan, etc.
It has the effect of replenishing qi and blood and calming the five internal organs.
Grandma, Mom
Going to the vegetable market to buy vegetables
What can buy
Go back and cook
To increase melatonin
Helps fall asleep. You can buy it like this
Sources of protein include
Eggs Fish Milk
Inside the fruit, there is
Grapes Kiwi Banana
Nuts have
Walnut, Almond and Black Sesame
Vegetables can be selected
Sweet potato leaves and spinach
Tomatoes, etc.
These foods are rich in tryptophan
Calcium, magnesium, and B complex
Helps stabilize nerves
Relax your mood and help you fall asleep
Top Sleep Aids: Meditation
Share with everyone
Me and my beautiful wife
A top-level sleep aid technique
that has been practiced for over 20 years
and scientifically proven
Called meditation
was nervous before
won't sleep well
Now after meditating
The mood is stable
Then what
Sleep better
When you go to bed at night
you just lie down and fall asleep
Yes, sleep better.
don't toss and turn
in my sleep like before.
Now at night
sleep well when lie down
And sleep more soundly
don't feel tired when get up
Feeling very refreshing
Really, also feel refreshed
after a good sleep.
The Key to Meditation
It
activates your
parasympathetic nervous system
This system
Like the commander-in-chief of relaxation for the body
It can help you get rid of the tense and anxious sympathetic nervous
state during the day
Switch to this rhythm
of repair and rest
You will find
Slow heartbeat
Lowered blood pressure
Deeper breathing
The mood also calmed down
This is the prelude
to the body entering sleep.
Really?
I often have this experience
It really happens
Many meditation practitioners
Including myself
Have experienced it personally
Fall asleep faster and sleep more deeply
More emotionally stable
Significant reduction in anxiety
Studies have long confirmed that
Meditation really does have a relaxing effect
Like the University of Illinois
Did an experiment
Let the subjects
Sit quietly for 5 to 10 minutes
turn out
Their brain oxygen consumption
Reduced by 17%
This change
It's like sleeping for 7 hours.
And the fatigue factor in the blood
That is lactic acid
Its concentration also decreased
Meditation can really help
Restores body and mind and drives away fatigue
There is a magazine in the United States called
JAMA Internal Medicine
This magazine says
What about people who practice mindfulness meditation for a long time?
Their sleep quality
and autonomic nervous system stability
significantly better than
those who did not meditate
Many scientific studies have confirmed
Sitting still can relieve pain
Improve concentration and immunity
It can also help lower blood pressure
Relieve anxiety and improve sleep
Even prevent depression
According to a 2007 survey
by the US government
There are more than 20 million people in the United States
Once had the experience of sitting in meditation
Global meditating population
It is estimated to have reached
275 million to 500 million people
Meditate and sleep well
Better than taking pills every day
Try it tonight
Sit quietly for 10 to 20 minutes
Turn off the lights before bed
Put down your phone and sit quietly
Hang the moon
Light up the stars
Let your brain calm down slowly
I hope you get a good night's sleep.
Clears toxins from the brain
Do you have meditation experience?
Welcome to leave a message
Share your experience with me
Two-minute sleep method
96% success rate
How to
fall asleep quickly
Let me teach you today
A magical
US Navy
two-minute sleep method
This was during World War II
A technique developed
by the US military
to solve the problem of insomnia in pilots
The task was very stressful.
Pilots often have trouble sleeping
Fatigue goes wrong
If the pilot makes a mistake
It's a matter of life and death.
So they developed a
Relaxation training
Fall asleep
in just two minutes
The method is very simple
Close your eyes and relax your jaw.
Shoulders, arms, chest and legs
Deep breath
Let your body sink
Then clear your mind
Imagine yourself floating on a lake
Or silently repeat: Don't think
This will help you
fall asleep quickly
within two minutes
Hearing you say that
I'm about to fall asleep
This hypnotic effect
seems to be really good
This trick even the pilots on the battlefield
Fall asleep within two minutes
After six weeks of training
A success rate of up to 96%
Try it tonight
Deep sleep clears brain waste
Prevent dementia
Many successful people
Once advocated short sleep
But now they are beginning to face
The importance of adequate sleep
Like Bill Gates
Because his father
Suffering from Alzheimer's disease
Get seven hours of sleep every day
No more forcing yourself to not sleep
Musk also said
Less than six hours of sleep
The brain hurts badly
Sleep is not a waste of time
It's the most important moment
for the brain to clean itself up.
When a person is in deep sleep
The brain clears a substance called
Waste products of beta-amyloid
Excessive accumulation of this protein
Will damage nerve cells
Affects memory
It may even lead to dementia
A study by the National Institutes of Health found
Healthy adults
After staying up for 30 hours
This protein in the brain
Started to accumulate
Another study
of 8,000 middle-aged
and elderly people found that
People who sleep less than six hours a night
Dementia risk
than those who sleep 7.8 hours
30% higher
Sleep until you are full and sleep well
people can be healthy and live long
Not only that
American Heart Association
Sleep is also listed
as one of the eight elements
to maintain cardiovascular health
Sufficient and good sleep can help
Repair blood vessels and strengthen immunity
Reduce chronic inflammation
Effectively prevent cardiovascular disease
Poor sleep is not just
Makes you feel depressed
More likely
Harmful to heart and brain health
Sleeping is the simplest
and most effective way
to completely eliminate fatigue.
Two major causes of insomnia
Make melatonin out of stock
Two common culprits of poor sleep
Always using your phone
head keeps thinking
Insufficient melatonin secretion
The more you lie down, the more awake you become
What do you think
about when you can't sleep?
want to sleep
The problem is that the brain
is like a late-night live broadcast
The sympathetic nervous system basically never gets off work
Don't lie hard on the bed
Tossing and turning only makes
the brain more tense
Stimulate sympathetic nerves
Inhibits the secretion of melatonin
Also caused
Difficulty falling asleep and light sleep
Finally there is one
The troublesome sleep killer
I know I know
Mobile phone
Blue light from mobile phones
It tricks the brain into thinking it's daytime
Melatonin is not secreted
The brain keeps turning on
The more you use it, the more awake you become.
Staying up late to browse the phone
Remind you
Don't look at your phone
for too long.
Experts have said
That way the phone will run out of battery.
Wake up the next day
You will get two dark circles haha
Is it harmful
if I look at it like this often?
Ha, staying up late is nothing big.
Just be careful in your next life.
Ha ha
Thank you to the members who recently joined our channel
Zhōu jì wén (transliteration)
Ching Ching
Chén yí yín(transliteration)
JC
WP Huang
With your support
I can continue to do
Better and more content
Sincerely invite you to join as a member
Be our warmest support
Go further together
Thanks